<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
messages here will be displayed on every user's homepage.
we should also have a way of auto publishing things to this xml file
xml format:
<notification>
	<date></date>
	<message></message>
<notification>

-->

<notifications>
	<notification>
		<date>February 7, 2011</date>
		<message>
			Welcome to the Alpha Release of ResMe!! We're glad you could join us. Before you go off and start clicking buttons&lt;br&gt;
			and messing with features, you should check out these pages first:&lt;br&gt;
			&lt;br&gt;The first, and most important, page you should check out is your &lt;a href='/privacy/'&gt;Privacy Settings&lt;/a&gt; page. With this, you can decide how&lt;br&gt;
			people interact with your profile.&lt;br&gt;
			&lt;br&gt;The second thing you should check out is our &lt;a href='#'&gt;About&lt;/a&gt; page, where you can learn about what ResMe is and what we can do&lt;br&gt;for you.&lt;br&gt;
      &lt;br&gt;Some other pages you'll find useful:
      &lt;ul&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href='/editprofile/'&gt;Profile Settings&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href='/editresumes/'&gt;Resume Management&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;/ul&gt;
		</message>
	</notification>

  <notification>
    <date>February, 8, 2011</date>
    <message>Testing the XML parser.</message>
  </notification>

	<notification>
		<date>dsafsdf</date>
		<message>
Wow, It's been a  long time since the last update. A lot of things have been changed as well as new
features being added! Hopefully I can list all the important ones here:
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
The homepage has been redesigned to make it easier for you to access specific things that might
interest you. Moving your mouse over the tabs on the left side and clicking them will let you change 
what is being displayed here. A brief explanation for each tab is provided below:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;ResMe News&lt;/b&gt; -- Any ResMe updates or deicsions that effect you will show up here. Be sure to check this 
often to stay on top of changes to ResMe!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Notifications&lt;/b&gt; -- Interactions between other ResMe users and you will be posted here.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;User Articles&lt;/b&gt; -- This section is designed specifically for ResMe users to share articles they find about
  the Economy, or the Job Market. You can also use this to share any advice you have.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Explore Resumes&lt;/b&gt; -- Resumes which we think might interest you are listed here. Maybe they're popular 
	resumes, or resumes in the same professoin as you either way, there might be something to learn.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Your Stack&lt;/b&gt; -- These are the resumes that you've chose to save.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;/ul&gt;
	&lt;br&gt;
	Another new feature that's been added is saving other people's resumes to your "stack". At the top of each profile
	is a button that will let you add or remove resumes from your stack. This is a convenient way
	to save resumes that you think are useful so you can easily look them up at a later time. You'll be notified of any 
	changes to resumes in your stack.
	&lt;br&gt;
	&lt;br&gt;
	The &lt;a href="/privacy/"&gt;Privacy Settings&lt;/a&gt; page has also been improved to be clearer and give you  more control 
	over how your resume is accessed. Be sure to check it out!
		</message>
	</notification>

</notifications>
